

Kareem El-Zomor

Front End Developer

Karim67899@gmail.com

01111258669

karim.website

in /kareem-el-zomoroa2a94150/

/KareeMagdyy

ABOUT

I am a Front End developer building websites and web applications. I specialize in HTML5, CSS3 & JavaScript, I'm also studying React and have a passion to be at the mastery level of Frontend Development. Take a look at my work \square !

SKILLS

• HTML 5

• CSS 3

• JavaScript

• BootStrap

• Git

Sass

EDUCATION

2013 – present Cairo, Egypt **Commerce**Cairo University

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

May 2019 – Jan 2021

Customer Service Advisor

Cairo, Egypt

SiriusXM Canada

Sep 2018 – Apr 2019 Cairo, Egypt Senior Closer

, 871

Global Expo Travel

Apr 2016 – Sep 2018

Sales Representative

Cairo, Egypt

EHM: Exhibition Housing Management

COURSES

Feb 2021

Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4 🗵

The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology

Apr 2021

CSS - The Complete Guide 2022 (incl. Flexbox, Grid & Sass) ☑

Udemy

Jun 2021

Responsive Web Design

FreeCodeCamp

Jun 2021

HTML & CSS ☑

IBM

Nov 2021

Interactivity with JavaScript 🖸

University of Michigan

LANGUAGES

ArabicNative

English Fluent